https://deerage.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy and Terms of Service
Privacy Policy and Terms of Service
INFORMATION PRIVACY POLICY
Your privacy is an important concern to us at Wildlife Analytical Laboratories. Our goal is to ensure a high level of security and confidentiality.
When you provide your personal information to Wildlife Analytical Laboratories (such as your name, address, phone number, company name, etc.) that information will NOT be sold, distributed, used, or given to any other company or individual for use in marketing or solicitation. We will maintain the confidentiality of your personal information and it will be used only to support your customer relationship with Wildlife Analytical Laboratories.
Additionally, any information gathered via a “cookie”, will not be shown, sold, distributed, used, or given to any other company or individual for their use. The cookies which we employ are used to gather browser and access statistical information only and are kept strictly confidential. If you have any questions regarding our policy, please email us.
Consider adding a certificate of aging to your order
Upgrade option available during checkout.
ORDER YOUR AGING KIT NOW
Its Almost Here!
PLEASE be patient with us as we are experiencing unprecedented growth! We are doing our best to keep up with kits and inquiries with our existing system which is not designed for this kind of volume. For fastest response send and email to customerservice@deerage.com. We are so grateful that business is flooding in but with the new system taking longer than expected it is VERY difficult to manage the incoming orders. As always we prioritize sample aging deadlines above all else. If you are trying to get through please hang in there and try email. Thank you!
New system will be in soon! CLICK HERE to see the exciting details
×
Pin It on Pinterest
